Joseph Stephen Cullinan Collection, 1895-1939
University of Houston Libraries
- Box List
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company,1928 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, 1928 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, Jan-May 1929 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, Jan-May 1929 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, June-Dec., 1929 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, 1931-37 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Dallas Petroleum Company, 1931-37 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - US Chamber of Commerce (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - US Chamber of Commerce (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - US Chamber of Commerce (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Art Collections, Paintings, Rings; American Public Highway (Pan Am); Engagements (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Art Collections, Paintings, Rings; American Public Highway (Pan Am); Engagements (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Art Collections, Paintings, Rings; American Public Highway (Pan Am); Engagements (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Art Collections, Paintings, Rings; American Public Highway (Pan Am); Engagements (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Financial Records (1 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Financial Records (2 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Financial Records (3 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Financial Records (4 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Income Tax, 1914-17 (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Income Tax, 1914-17 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Income Tax, 1918-35 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Income Tax, 1918-35 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Material Concerning Oil Surveys, 1913-15 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Correspondence, 1919-28 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Correspondence, 1929-36 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Correspondence, 1929-36 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Family Vacations, 1927-31 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Family Vacations, 1927-31 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Family Tree (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - US Emergency Fleet Corp., 1917; War Financing, 1917-19; Film, "The Yanks Are Coming" (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Investments; Accounting-general 1912-14; Letters of Instructions, etc. JSC to BWW [ard]; Insurance; Rentals and Leases; Chemical National Bank, Central Pet. Stk. (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Investments; Accounting-general (1912-14); Letters of Instructions, etc: JSC to BWW[ard];Insurance; Rentals and Leases; Chemical National Bank, Central Pet. Stock (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Correspondence 1937 (1 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Correspondence 1937 (2 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Correspondence 1937 (3 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Donations and Gifts, 1934-35 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Donations and Gifts, 1934-35 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Donations and Gifts, Jan-July 1936 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Donations and Gifts, Jan-July 1936 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Donations and Gifts, Aug. 1936-37 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Donations and Gifts, Aug. 1936-37 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Estate of James L Autry (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Estate of James L Autry (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Estate of James L Autry (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Estate of James L Autry (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Estate of James L Autry (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Estate of James L Autry: current statement; closing statement of JLA; estate of James L Autry Jr. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Mrs James L Autry & Miss Allie May Autry Trusts (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Mrs James L Autry & Miss Allie May Autry Trusts (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Mrs James L Autry & Miss Allie May Autry Trusts (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Miss Allie May Autry Trusts (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Miss Allie May Autry Trusts (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Allie May Trust-Edward W Kelly Loan (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. Allie May Autry Kelly Estate (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. Allie May Autry Kelly Estate (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan - Sale of Assets (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan - Sale of Assets (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan - Sale of Assets (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Estate of Lucie Halm Cullinan (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - John H Cullinan Estate (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - John H Cullinan Estate (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - John H Cullinan Estate (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - John H Cullinan (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - John H Cullinan (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Sawyer Estate, 1911-31 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Sawyer Estate, 1911-31 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Sawyer Estate, 1932-37 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Sawyer Estate, 1932-37 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - W.B. Sharp Estate, 1912-21 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - W.B. Sharp Estate, 1917-21 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - W.B. Sharp Estate, 1917-21 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - W.B. Sharp Estate,1912-21 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - W.B. Sharp Estate, 1917-21 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, National River & Harbors Congress, 1912-1914 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, National River & Harbors Congress, 1915 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, National River & Harbors Congress, 1916 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, National River & Harbors Congress, 1917 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, National River & Harbors Congress, 1918 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, National River & Harbors Congress, 1930-31 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, NIRA Park, 1933-34 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, NIRA Park, 1935-37 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, National Reclamation Association, 1915 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Federal Investment Company, 1922-36 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Houston Foreign Trade Association, 1935-36, 1916-20 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, George Peabody Association for Teachers, 1926-32 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, National Recreation Association, 1934-37 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1926-28 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Donation and Gifts (Christmas 1931-37) (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Donation and Gifts (Christmas 1931-37) (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Donation and Gifts (Christmas 1931-37) (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Dogs & Fairs (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Cigars, 1916-37 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Clothing and Shoes (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Child Labor Amendment (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Child Labor Amendment (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Child Labor Amendment (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Child Labor Amendment (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Christmas Cards, 1934, 1935, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Current Bills, Accounting, 1921-37 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Cotton (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Obituaries-JSC's Death, March 11, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Ava Aircraft Corp. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Ava Aircraft Corp. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Coline Oil Company (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Coline Oil Company (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Development Realty Company (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Federal Investment Company - Bailey Lumber Co. Property, 1924-28 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Federal Investment Company - Bailey Lumber Co. Property, 1929-36 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Federal Investment Company - Misc Correspondence, 1915-25 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Federal Investment Company - Misc Correspondence, 1926-32 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Federal Investment Company - Misc Correspondence, 1926-32 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Federal Investment Company - Misc Correspondence, 1933-37 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Instructions concerning JS Cullinan's Correspondence, 1923-37 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1914-15 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1914-15 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1916 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1917-18 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1919-1920 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1919-1920 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1919-1920 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Washington D.C., 1914-23 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Washington D.C., 1914-23 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Washington D.C., 1924-37 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Washington D.C., 1924-37 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Client Securities, 1919-23 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Client Securities, 1919-23 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Client Securities, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Client Securities, 1927-28 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Client Securities, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Client Securities, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Client Securities, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Client Securities, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Client Securities, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Client Securities, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Client Securities, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Leases and Rentals, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence & Papers Concerning WC Hogg (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence & Papers Concerning WC Hogg (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Maps of Land, Mineral and Oil Leases (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1936-37 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1936-37 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Securities, Personal (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Accounts Payable, 1922-24; Estate of WN Long, 1929-33 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Client Securities, 1914-21 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Client Securities, 1920-37 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Client Securities, 1926 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Client Securities, 1927-36 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Client Securities, 1927-36 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Client Securities, 1913-25 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Client Securities, 1923-25 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Fidelity Trust Company, 1923-25 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Fidelity Trust Company, 1923-25 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Fidelity Trust Company, 1926-27 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Fidelity Trust Company, 1926-27 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Clients Securities (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Clients Securities (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Clients Securities (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Clients Securities, GSO, 1919-30 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Clients Securities, GSO, 1919-30 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Clients Securities, 1924-28 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Clients Securities, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Clients Securities, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Clients Securities, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Clients Securities, 1928 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Clients Securities, 1929-30 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Clients Securities,1931 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Clients Securities,1931 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Clients Securities,1932 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Clients Securities,1932 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Clients Securities,1937, 1939, 1923-36 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - American Republic Corporation, Stocks, 1919-27 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - American Republic Corporation, Stocks, 1919-27 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - American Republic Corporation, Stocks, 1928-36 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1915-27 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1915-27 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1923-31 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1932-34 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1932-34 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1935 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Hardy Mining Company, 1936-37 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Hardy Mining Company, Financial Statements, 1933-37 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Hardy Mining Company, Organizations and Meetings, 1923-36 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Hardy Mining Company, Taxes, 1925-36 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Green Real Estate, 1916-30 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Green Real Estate, 1916-30 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Green Real Estate (Texas and Carolina), 1930-37 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1924-26 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1927-30 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1927-30 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1931-36 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm, 1931-36 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Concerning Pipeline Leases, 1936-37 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Santa Anna Farm - Wharf and Channel Frontage, 1915, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Concerning Monument on Santa Anna Farm, 1915-16 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence Concerning Proposed Incorporation of Pasadena, 1924-30 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Santa Anna Farm - Houston Lighting and Power Co Easement, 1922-24 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Client Securities, 1928 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Client Securities, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Client Securities, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Emma G. Mills Estate, 1920-23 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Pedigrees and Tabulated Records (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Emma G. Mills Estate, 1924-31 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Emma G. Mills Estate, 1932-36 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Hardy Oil Company-Financial Statements, 1924-34 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Wheeler Oil Field Leases and Rentals, 1910-16 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Corsicana Real Estate, 1921-23 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Downtown Property, 1915-1934 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Hermann Property, 1916 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Washington D.C. Real Estate, Wyoming Ave. 1922-30 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Washington D.C. Real Estate, Wyoming Ave. 1931-36 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Transportation, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Transportation, Oct.-Dec. 1930 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Transportation, Jan 1931-Dec 1932 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Transportation, Jan-March, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Transportation, April-June, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Transportation, July-Sept, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Transportation, Oct-Dec, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Transportation, 1934 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Transportation, 1935 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Transportation, 1936 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Northern Properties Negotiations: General American Transportation Corp., May-Oct, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Northern Properties Negotiations: General American Transportation Corp., Nov-Dec, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Northern Properties Negotiations: General American Transportation Corp., 1933 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Farmer's Petroleum Company, 1922-23 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Irish Company, 1922-23 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - American Republics Corp., 1917-1921 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - American Republics Corp., 1933 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - American Republics Corp., 1934 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - American Republics Corp., March-May 1934 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - American Republics Corp., Jan-April 1935 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - American Republics Corp., May-December, 1935 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - American Republics Corp., 1936-37 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1924-26 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1928 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - American Republics Corp., Preferred Stock Correspondence, 1933-1936 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - 20 Miscellaneous: 1) Autry, J.L.; 2) Autry prior to 12/31/18 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous: 1) Autry, J.L.; 2) Autry prior to 12/31/18 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: 1) Kipp, H.A.; 2) Armstrong, G.W.; 3) Brahany, T.W. (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: 4) Bracken, Clio, Mrs.; 5) Denning, L.E. (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: 1) Clients Securities (Ruth Curtin); 2) Colquitt, O.B. (misc); 3) Crosbie, J.E. (misc); 4) Clede, Ivan (artist); 5) Clancy, Maria, Mrs. (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: Clancy, J.L. (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: 1) Chidsey, I.P.; 2) Thomson, J.D.; 3)Dennig, L.E. (misc); 4) Eagle, Joe H (personal) (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: Joe H Eagle (loan) (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: Joe H Eagle (loan) (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: Joe H Eagle (loan) (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Misc. Papers Concerning: 1) Edson, J.A.; 2) Garrison, Elva S., Mrs.; 3) J.A. Handy vs. Mutual Life Ins Co.; 4) Legal Dept and Litigation; 5) JSC Personal Accounts and Statements (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Richland Quarry Co.-misc. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Richland Quarry Co.-misc. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - 1) Southern Trust Co., misc.; 2) Straughan Henrietta Oil Co-Loan; 3) The Texas Wagon Works; 4) Tulsa Boiler and Mfg Co. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - 5) Utah, misc.; 6) Tulsa Boiler and Sheet Iron Works (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Southern Transportation Co., 1912-16 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - The Texas Oil Co., 1913-15 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Sales Tax, Anti Tax Association (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Sales Tax, Anti Tax Association (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Sales Tax, Anti Tax Association (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Concerning Col. Tim Spellacy (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning Col. Henry B Lindsey (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning Beverly D Harris (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Taxation, Texas Tax Relief Committee (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Taxation, Texas Tax Relief Committee (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Taxation - a) Real Estate, 1933-36; b) comparative tax statements; c)Misc. 1934-36 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous - 1) Agriculture; 2) Allied Bazaar, 1916; 3) Americanization; 4) Aviation Service (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous - 5) "Bell Hops" Hotel America; 6) Corpus Christy Port Development Association; 7) Corpus Christi, Storm 1919; 8) Council of National Defense, 1918; 9) Monthly Rental Statements (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous - 10) Real Estate Records; 11) Houston Real Estate Board; 12) Real Estate Convention, Houston January 23-26, 1935 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous - 10) Real Estate Records; 11) Houston Real Estate Board; 12) Real Estate Convention, Houston January 23-26, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous - 10) Real Estate Records; 11) Houston Real Estate Board; 12) Real Estate Convention, Houston January 23-26, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Propositions Submitted 1931-37 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Propositions Submitted 1931-37 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - 1) Utah Oil Refining Co., 1915; 2) USS Corp, 1914-15; 3) Ventura Oil & Gas, Misc; 4) Ventura Oil & Gas, Statements 1915-16; 5) West Tulsa Beltway Railway Co., 1913-15 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning Dr. Charles McCarthy (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning Dr. Charles McCarthy (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning Dr. Charles McCarthy (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning 1) Silsbee, Frank J; 2) series of articles about the Houston ship channel by Thos H Bell (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Interior Dept., misc. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Interior Dept., misc. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - 12 Correspondence & Papers concerning 1) Negro Mutiny in Houston, 1917 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning 2) Hermann Park; 3) Houston City Planning; 4) Electricity Rates and Requi); 5) Heneraries; 6) Misc. Real Estates (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Real Estate, JSC, personal (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning 1) Office; 2) Transportation; 3) Univ. Organization (UT); Suffrage (women) (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning 1) Coal; 2) WWI - misc.; 3) Maps, Blue Prints (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence & Papers concerning 4) Federal Farm Land Bank; 5) Real Estate (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Railway Freight Rates, 1914-16 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Chauffeurs Applications, 1921 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - 1) Summer Trips, 1915; 2) "Is American Gassed?" 1919 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Chauffeurs Applications, 1921 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Producer's Oil Co., 1913-1920 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Producer's Oil Co., 1913-1920 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Producer's Oil Co., Financial Records (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Producer's Oil Co., Financial Records (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Producer's Oil Co., Texas Co., Organizations, 1913 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Producer's Oil Co., Stocks (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Producer's Oil Co., Stocks (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Producer's Oil Co. & Cullinan vs. Texas Co. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Producer's Oil Co. & Cullinan vs. Texas Co. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Producer's Oil Co. & Cullinan vs. Texas Co. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Producer's Oil Co. & Cullinan vs. Texas Co. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Cullinan vs. Texas Co. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Securities (Cullinan vs. Texas Co.) (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Securities (Cullinan vs. Texas Co.) (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Copy of Minutes, Producer's Oil Co (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Northside Belt Railway - General Correspondence, 1926-28 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Northside Belt Railway - General Correspondence, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Northside Belt Railway - General Correspondence, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Financial Records, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Financial Records, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Financial Records, 1927-28 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Financial Records, 1929-31 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Balance Sheets, 1931-36 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Accounting and Reports, 1926-37 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Construction, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Proposed Issuance of Bonds, 1925-26 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Correspondence Concerning Proposed Sale, 1925-26 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Judge Phillips Pamphlet, 1925-26 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Northside Belt Railway - First Mortgage and Deed of Trust, 1925-26 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Maps, 1926, 1928, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Meetings, 1926-1937 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Northside Belt Railway - Construction, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, M.P. Cullinan Estate, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, M.P. Cullinan Estate, 1928-1934 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, M.P. Cullinan Estate, 1935-37 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: (A) (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: (B) (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinan) & C, 1914 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1915 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: "C" (the Cullinans) & C, 1915 (Box 57, Folder 23)